<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kaitlyn Richardson</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kaitlyn Richardson</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Blog Post</title>
      <link>/post/2021/05/09/blog-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021/05/09/blog-post/</guid>
      <description>Hey guys! Check out my work:Link to project 1
Also, more importantly, check out my dog!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: Exploratory Data Analysis</title>
      <link>/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>knitr::opts_chunk$set(echo = TRUE, eval = TRUE, fig.align = &amp;quot;center&amp;quot;, warning = F, message = F, tidy=TRUE, tidy.opts=list(width.cutoff=60), R.options=list(max.print=100)) library(plyr)
0. Introduction For project one, I chose to play with Spotify data and Austin’s weather data. Initially, I choose the Spotify data because I was really interested in what all I had been listening to throughout the pandemic. In the data, I could see what artist I listened to on a certain day, the song I listened to, what time it played, and how many milliseconds I played them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Modeling, Testing, and Predicting</title>
      <link>/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>#0: Data Description My project 2 data is a cross section of patients who visit a physician’s office and the emergency room. I chose this data because I thought the numerical data including patient’s age, sex, race, family income, office visits, ER emissions, hospitalizations and number of chronic illnesses would be interesting to manipulate. Naturally, I have certain biases of how the healthcare system works, and due to the large sample size (4406 observations), I thought this would be a wonderful way of measuring those biases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description> Check out some of my coding projects below:
 Wrangling &amp;amp; Exploratory Data Analysis
 Modeling, Inference, Prediction
  -- </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>Kaitlyn Richardson
918-760-1909
kkr647@utexas.edu
CAREER OBJECTIVE
Hard-working and eager biology student. Interested in gaining more experience in the healthcare setting. Aiming to leverage skills to become a physician assistant. Special interest in cultural topics of public health, emerging infectious diseases, and genetic disorders.
PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE
THE UNIVERSITY OF TEXAS AUSTIN COLLEGE OF BIOSCIENCES Austin, TX Undergraduate Genetics TA for Janice Fischer, Aug 2020 – Dec 2020 Aid in student learning, prepare class topics, grade class activities, provide tutoring in a classroom setting.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
